chevybeat.co.in 2010-07-27

# Chevrolet india

Neither you, nor General Motors Corporation including its subsidiaries like GMI (“GM”) would want that your personal information falls into the wrong hands. When you visit one of the GM Web sites, GM may collect and store information about your visit on GM systems. This information may include your personal information, name of your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. GM may use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving GM sites, for the benefit of GM’s prospective customers.

There are also several opportunities on GM’s Web sites for you to provide us your personal information including your name, mailing address, e-mail address and your interests. If you choose to share any personal information with GM, we may store it and use it for our research and/or other marketing/sales related purposes, which may include sharing it with other companies in the GM family and GM’s business partners.

You may note that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on GM’s Web site(s), such as chat rooms or bulletin boards, this information may be seen and used by others. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these areas.

Some of GM’s Web sites may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. So, when you come back to visit GM’s site again, GM can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save your time and provide you with a more meaningful visit.

The price stated here has been generally checked for accuracy but is subject to change at sole discretion of GM and is subject to applicable taxes. The contents of this page is subject to change without prior notice. Neither General Motors India Private Limited ("GMI") nor its dealers assumes responsibility for any pricing errors. In the event a vehicle is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information inadvertently, GMI or its dealers shall have the right to refuse any orders, which is based on incorrect price/information.

GM reserves the right to alter the privacy principles as business needs may require from time to time. Any amendments to these principles will be available on GM Web sites in a timely manner.
